export default data = [
  {
      question: "I have to catch the bus right now, ______ I'll miss my brother's birthday party",
      options: ["and","because","or","until"],
      correct_option: "or"
  },
  {
      question: "Oliver ______ with joy when he saw his favorite band. He kept saying loudly, I love you guys!",
      options: ["waited","shouted","listened","agreed"],
      correct_option: "shouted"
  },
  {
      question: "Ms. Lee is a(n) ______ businesswoman. Just now in her shop, she gave me back the wallet I left on the table last week",
      options: ["famous","honest","important","smart"],
      correct_option: "honest"
  },
  {
      question: "Lexie ______ reading maps. Even with a map, she still cannot find her way when she is in a foreign city",
      options: ["is careful about","is good at","has fun","has trouble"],
      correct_option: "has trouble"
  },
  {
      question: "More and more cows on this farm are getting sick.  The problem is so ______ that the farm will be closed from tomorrow on",
      options: ["heavy","popular","serious","strong"],
      correct_option: "serious"
  },
  {
      question: "Some songs are forgotten very quickly. A really good song can pass the test of ______ and be remembered for many, many years",
      options: ["knowledge","sound","time","weather"],
      correct_option: "time"
  },
  {
      question: "I'm not sure if Kevin ______ this morning, but if he does, I'll tell him that you called",
      options: ["will come in","comes in","has come in","came in"],
      correct_option: "will come in"
  },
  {
      question: "I think the road ends here; it won't go any ______ Shouldn't we turn back?",
      options: ["closer","farther","faster","longer"],
      correct_option: "farther"
  },
  {
      question: "Jogging is the only exercise I enjoy. I find ______ other kinds of exercise boring",
      options: ["all","few","many","some"],
      correct_option: "all"
  },
  {
      question: "Smart Head, one of the hottest TV programs these days, ______ people free plane tickets to Hawaii if they can answer 20 questions correctly in 15 minutes",
      options: ["have given","gives","giving","to give"],
      correct_option: "gives"
  },
  {
      question: "Helen: Can you turn off the TV?  I can't study with the ______. Troy: You can just go back to your room so you won't hear it",
      options: ["noise","heat","power","light"],
      correct_option: "noise"
  },
]
